<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Girlfriend on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/girlfriend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Girlfriend on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 16:16:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/girlfriend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>the world never stops</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/10/08/the-world-never-stops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 16:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/10/08/the-world-never-stops/</guid>
      <description>this is the best quote I have heard in many moons. 
ANGORA8: my friend&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend always wears corduroy and it sounds like gerbils screaming between her thighs 
haha. so awesome. tonight I am going to a kerry thing. hopefully it won&amp;rsquo;t suck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost there</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/10/28/almost-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2001 17:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/10/28/almost-there/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend my girlfriend came, it was great. I had a wonderful wonderful time. Another two weeks and it will be one year. A year is a long time, like k*star said this morning, &amp;ldquo;a year has one of eveything in it.&amp;rdquo; I never realized it - but it is true. Together we have been through almost everything. how nice. I enjoy it so so much. Walking last night, we found one of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/10/10/anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2001 23:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/10/10/anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Today I saw the band Anniversary. They were interesting. Not really as good as I thought. It is weird when you go see a lot of bands that you listen to often ? I feel I know every lick, every lyric and every guitar riff, and when the band does something creative in concert it annoys me. Luckily with bands like modest mouse, the creativity is very solid ? and with built to spill, they were right on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/01/02/ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2001 04:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/01/02/ireland/</guid>
      <description>Today has been good, well the whole break has been good. my friend amanda is here visiting. its nice and fun. I had a good first of the year. it was a good time. we went to denver and chilled.. then went to boulder.. i guess the main thing that is effecting me right now is the absence of my girlfriend.. she is of course visting her familia in chitown.. alas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>