<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology Technology on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/technology-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology Technology on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 23:50:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/technology-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rails woes. The slow that is keeping twitter down.</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2007/04/15/rails-woes.-the-slow-that-is-keeping-twitter-down./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2007 23:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2007/04/15/rails-woes.-the-slow-that-is-keeping-twitter-down./</guid>
      <description>I have a love and hate relationship with Ruby on Rails. I love what it does. I love the activerecord, I love how it makes designers and other non-software engineers into raving MVC lunatics. I really like coding in ruby and seeing how much work can get done by so little code. All of that is really exciting. However, I hate a lot about rails as well. I do not like that it is so slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eAccelerator made it faster!</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2007/02/14/eaccelerator-made-it-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2007 13:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2007/02/14/eaccelerator-made-it-faster/</guid>
      <description>So my blog has been slow for the past few months. It has been killing me. I run my own server - so I knew it was something that I did. However, I sadly thought that it was probably just the fact that I have a couple rather high bandwidth sites and only one server. I tried a lot of the &amp;ldquo;speed up wordpress&amp;rdquo; tricks and even installed and used wp-cache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Vista vs OSX - Price comparison</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2007/01/17/windows-vista-vs-osx-price-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2007 11:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2007/01/17/windows-vista-vs-osx-price-comparison/</guid>
      <description>So Jake asked me about Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s new Windows Vista and whether we should look into getting it. So we looked at the website to see when it comes out and wtf - it doesn&amp;rsquo;t say. hah. It totally says that the countdown starts now, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell me when the countdown ends. What a horrible website. Jake thought it was a spam site at first and only from it being at the domain Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I setup blogs for my friends</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2007/01/15/how-i-setup-blogs-for-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2007 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2007/01/15/how-i-setup-blogs-for-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>I am a blog advocate. I am often pushing my friends to get blogs and to update them. I love reading about how my friends are doing and what is going on in their lives and with their friends. It is such a nifty way to stay in touch. I know from my own experience how rewarding blogging can be. How it can create connections with people who normally would never be connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to hook twitter into a IRC channel</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/12/12/how-to-hook-twitter-into-a-irc-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2006 02:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/12/12/how-to-hook-twitter-into-a-irc-channel/</guid>
      <description>So I love playing with fancy things. And twitter is one of those fancy things. In fact - it has been on my mind quite a bit. Like I said a couple posts ago, I have been thinking about writing a utility that will set your IM status based on your twitter update. It will be awesome. But in the meantime I whipped up a quick hack to help yall hook your twitter into your IRC application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twapp - a quick hack to update and view twitter</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/12/07/twapp-a-quick-hack-to-update-and-view-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2006 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/12/07/twapp-a-quick-hack-to-update-and-view-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Tonight after work I decided to whip up a quick twitter client in C#. I love C#. It is so fun and easy. I have never done web work in it, but love writing applications. So tonight I just sat down and slugged through the idea.
You can check it out at: http://flashandburn.net/twapp
The idea behind the client is a small application that will sit in your taskbar and constantly update you on your friend timeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux distribution for older folks.</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/12/05/linux-distribution-for-older-folks./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2006 00:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/12/05/linux-distribution-for-older-folks./</guid>
      <description>So my grandfather is older. He isn&#39;t 1000, nor is he 150. But he is up there. Maybe around 75ish. But he is pretty spry and active. He is, in fact, the mayor of his town. So the other day when I was in Colorado - he mentioned how he was needing to get his emails up, how he needed to be able to get and receive his important mayoral emails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuff.harperreed.org. Last nights web-dev itch</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/11/24/stuff.harperreed.org.-last-nights-web-dev-itch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2006 20:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/11/24/stuff.harperreed.org.-last-nights-web-dev-itch/</guid>
      <description>So last night after watching movies with my parents and making capes with my mom, I decided to redo my code repository/misc directory site that was at nata2.info. I decided that I needed to make my code repository a bit more &#34;official&#34; - so I moved everything that was at nata2.info over to stuff.harperreed.org. Then&amp;nbsp;I rewrote the blorp script that was powering the repository using PHP and smarty. I used the Pear TEXT/Highlighter class to colorize the source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking mobile voicemail with Asterisk and caller ID spoofing</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/09/24/hacking-mobile-voicemail-with-asterisk-and-caller-id-spoofing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2006 23:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/09/24/hacking-mobile-voicemail-with-asterisk-and-caller-id-spoofing/</guid>
      <description>So there has always had a problem with US mobile providers having their voicemail be susceptible to being compromised by calling with a spoofed caller id. Apparently most providers caller id apps just checks the referring callerid - and doesn&amp;rsquo;t force the voicemail user to pick a passcode; so it allows someone to trick the voicemail app into believing they are calling from a trusted number.
This has been covered all over the Internet and was in the spotlight awhile back when it was alleged that this was how Paris Hilton&amp;rsquo;s mobile phone was hacked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts about The DECK and PageRank.</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/09/18/thoughts-about-the-deck-and-pagerank./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 16:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/09/18/thoughts-about-the-deck-and-pagerank./</guid>
      <description>The other day I read the great post about Matt Cutt&#39;s SEO tips and tricks that were gleaned from his great blog. It was probably one of the most helpful SEO articles I had read in a minute. It summarized some points that I had learned throughout the years with just a couple sentences. Good work.
While the article was still fresh in my mind I was talking to Jacob about how our host, rackspace, now advertises on the DECK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to sync your phone, iCal and Google Calendar together.</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/07/24/how-to-sync-your-phone-ical-and-google-calendar-together./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2006 04:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/07/24/how-to-sync-your-phone-ical-and-google-calendar-together./</guid>
      <description>I use a lot of operating systems in my daily computing exercise, each one does its own thing. I use windows for development - which really means that i just use windows for putty and firefox. I use linux to host and write code. and i use OSX for personal information management. Today i am going to tell yall how i use the i-suite and Google Calendar to have my calendars accessible all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Apart&#39;s Vox - nice work.. good aggregation... but i don&#39;t want another blog. </title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2006/07/18/six-aparts-vox-nice-work..-good-aggregation...-but-i-dont-want-another-blog./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2006 03:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2006/07/18/six-aparts-vox-nice-work..-good-aggregation...-but-i-dont-want-another-blog./</guid>
      <description>So tonight i have been playing with Six Aparts VOX blog service. Besides the confusing name (probably only confusing to me - the alcoholic podcaster) Six Aparts social network blog thing is pretty cool. Check out my profile here and my &amp;ldquo;blog&amp;rdquo; here. I like the idea behind the VOX social network. I have long thought that SA is pretty smooth at executing products. The Movable Type platform was always nice looking and easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>