<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Job on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2004 16:36:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>enders gamer</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/10/01/enders-gamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2004 16:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/10/01/enders-gamer/</guid>
      <description>I am officially done with work today. super weird. i get to start my new job on monday. the end of an era and all that jazz. but whatever. it is gunna be a fun and new experience. hehe. sounds lame but it is true. my coworker just asked me if i was a world book employee - i was all &amp;ldquo;nope&amp;rdquo; and he tackled me.
well now it is off to my &amp;ldquo;party&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i am reading an incredibly rough book</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/08/19/i-am-reading-an-incredibly-rough-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2003 06:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/08/19/i-am-reading-an-incredibly-rough-book/</guid>
      <description>it isn&amp;rsquo;t hard per se. it is just rough. it is called Into That Darkness. it is about the Franz Stangl the commandant of treblinka. When I first started reading the book - I thought &amp;ldquo;oh.. I can handle this.. it won&amp;rsquo;t be rought.. I have read about this stuff before.&amp;rdquo; little did I know.. i think what is hard for me to understand is how workers at the extermination camps seemed to rationalize the killing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tonight.. Tonight.. Tonight.. Tonight</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/01/25/tonight..-tonight..-tonight..-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2002 07:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/01/25/tonight..-tonight..-tonight..-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Well. Tonight I slept. Well I went to a bar after work with coworkers got a little tippsy and ate a hamburger.. came home and slept till eleven. and then negated any sleep by staying up way late. I then watched a bunch of TV and rotted my mind. Sometimes.. I feel like contirbuting to the delinquency of my palm pilot. So I keep looking at all the nifty INFOSEC stuff available right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two things</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/09/27/two-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2001 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/09/27/two-things/</guid>
      <description>First, I really miss block breaks. I am horribly stuck. I wish my company was a more liberal dot com. I wish it was 99-2000 and I was a high profile consultant. I really wish that the company I work for was interested in making the employees happy. WHich they seemingly arn&amp;rsquo;t. It seems that profit is the key, but even when I can identify things which are easy and would save money - getting them approved would cost more money then the initial savings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>