<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Server on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Server on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2004 14:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>sux0r</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/04/09/sux0r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2004 14:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/04/09/sux0r/</guid>
      <description>so my l33t skills didn&amp;rsquo;t work out today. I totally screwed up my servers. well not really. I am not on my new servers yet. I had to leave my old server in colo - which costs me a lot more money, and I had to use the switch- so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to return it. it sucks. I am pretty pissed/upset. mostly cuz I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lock and block</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/01/28/lock-and-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2004 22:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/01/28/lock-and-block/</guid>
      <description>I have been workign nigths for WB doing load testing and such - and it is so weird being up from 10-4 or so and then sleeping as much as you can from 4-10 haha. it is hard on me. I get tired real easy and I totally don&amp;rsquo;t have the stamina to run around and be merry today. Luckily last night was one of the last ones for awhile. work is going well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hot hot hot</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/06/23/hot-hot-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2003 23:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/06/23/hot-hot-hot/</guid>
      <description>i am sittin ghere without a lot of clothes on listneing to pinback. they are good. it is hot out. I am sleepy. heh .i hate the commute home. it is not much at all.. but is enough to make me want a sleeping car on the el. stupid el. stupid sleep. today I spent all day debuggin g a chroot environment on one of our web servers. it seems that you have to be awefully particular with tthe permissions when the chrott is on a mounted drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WooHooo</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/04/20/woohooo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2003 19:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/04/20/woohooo/</guid>
      <description>So friday night was the fischerspooner show. it was really quite something. I enjoyed the calculated mistakes and insanity that made up the show. The guys seemed really great as well. Very funny. I loved the break away clothing. and all my friend were their. Here are pictures from the &amp;ldquo;afterparty.&amp;rdquo; never mind my crotch.. it wasn&amp;rsquo;t my fault..Right now I am sitting outside in the sun.. working on my new server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server send off...</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/08/15/server-send-off.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2001 18:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/08/15/server-send-off.../</guid>
      <description>So i sent off my server today. It was wierd just packing it in a box and sending it to someone whom i have never met or really talked to a lot. The place that is cohostin git seems kinda sketchy, but at the same time also seems really cool. They are a backbone provider for Ohio State, and the State of Ohio :)&amp;hellip; so the bandwidth will be good - and i will be hooked pretty much directly on the backbone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>