<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Women on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>http://harper.blog/tags/women/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Women on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2003 07:16:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://harper.blog/tags/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>tonight.. heh..</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2003/08/16/tonight..-heh../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2003 07:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2003/08/16/tonight..-heh../</guid>
      <description>tonight was incredible. I went on a date with this really great women. heh. we went to a show.. which was brilliant. and then went to eat at innjoy.. then went to her house and watched a bit of pulp fiction. it was altogether really nice. she was smart and fun. and full of good conversation. it is nice to meet some one who isn&amp;rsquo;t dumb. hehe. w00t</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>passing me by</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2003/04/29/passing-me-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2003 14:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2003/04/29/passing-me-by/</guid>
      <description>So this really attractive and well dressed women stood accross from me on the train today. She kept smiling at me and generally making me uncomfortable. Of course.. I didn&amp;rsquo;t say anything like hi or bye or anything. just walked off like a goon. doh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>omg wtf</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2002/04/19/omg-wtf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2002 21:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2002/04/19/omg-wtf/</guid>
      <description>So a a friend found one of the most bizarre collection of pictures in awhile: here. It seems that this dude mike(as far as I can tell that is him) likes to have pictures of women. But the repository also has a lot of personal pictures as well. It just gets my voyeuristic juices a flowin. that along with MOC an weblog reading of course. i normally don&amp;rsquo;t want to post shite like those pics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grep</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2002/01/26/grep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2002 01:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2002/01/26/grep/</guid>
      <description>Today at work we discussed what unix utility we would take on a deserted island if we hand to choose one or two. I choose grep and regular expressions. So you could globally replace bananas with women. heh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane&#39;s Addiction</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2001/10/21/janes-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2001 23:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2001/10/21/janes-addiction/</guid>
      <description>I saw Jane&amp;rsquo;s Addiction tonight. it was a great show. very Very good. Perry Farrell too koff his clothes and danced around in his polo underwear and calvin klein socks. very humerous. I much enjoyed it. They had dancing very almost naked women. It was quite something. Well goodnight&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>