<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2001 10:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Built to Spill</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/09/08/built-to-spill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2001 10:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/09/08/built-to-spill/</guid>
      <description>I went to built to spill tonight. It was a good time. They played freebird as the last song. It was very very good. I enjoyed it quite a lot. Doug(if that is his name) was a good guitar player. The audience was OK, Except for some assholes who were harrasing a simple drunk man. I was sad for him. But eventually the dumbasses were kicked out.. weee..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn!! It is Hot!!!</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/08/01/damn-it-is-hot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2001 03:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/08/01/damn-it-is-hot/</guid>
      <description>It is so hot here in chi-town. I have never been in such an inferno degree. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind it really, but it is so relentless. I sit here trying to code, tryin gto read waiting for something to happen. For it to get cooler. For someone to tell me &amp;ldquo;hey, its nice and cool over here&amp;rdquo; but&amp;hellip; nothing makes it better. and time only makes it worse&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goddamn Hosting Providers</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/07/10/goddamn-hosting-providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2001 04:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/07/10/goddamn-hosting-providers/</guid>
      <description>So my did in fact inadvertantly deleted all of the info on one of my servers. I called and asked
&amp;ldquo;why&amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;well, it had a kernal problem.. it needed a reburn&amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;have you heard of a boot disk?&amp;ldquo;
I guess not huh&amp;hellip; well damnit.. heh i guess everything is OK. i didn&amp;rsquo;t lose anything special - just 40hrs of fresh php virtual host admin tools, about 30hrs of mysql work, 20hrs of system stuff, and about 10hrs of system configuration&amp;hellip; alas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typographic illustrations</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/07/09/typographic-illustrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2001 20:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/07/09/typographic-illustrations/</guid>
      <description>Check out this. Some really beautiful typographic illustrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2001/02/15/valentines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2001 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2001/02/15/valentines/</guid>
      <description>I had a valentine for this years valentines day. It was really neat. I never expected myself to become interested in romance. I like it though. I have never before felt this way about anyone. It is crazy. Valentines day was incredible. it was fun, romantic and all that.. On another note, i am in a fun fun electronics course. I wrote an oscilliscope/function-generator for a digital acquisition board we use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2000/11/04/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2000 09:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2000/11/04/program/</guid>
      <description>I now need to write a program to update this.. so i can email a specific email address or log on to a specific page and update my journal.. hehe wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be cool to be able to update my journal from my palm pilot.. wooha&amp;hellip; thats right.. maybe i should add a spell checker and a url format-er as well.. hmmm so much to do.. so much time :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2000/11/03/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2000 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2000/11/03/first-post/</guid>
      <description>I added this journal/diary/update program i wrote. It is getting stupid easy to create random programs for my web page. I just hope that someday all of this effort will pay off&amp;hellip; Hehe.. like it hasn&amp;rsquo;t already :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>milestone</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2000/03/01/milestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2000 23:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2000/03/01/milestone/</guid>
      <description>Today, after class, i walked from the library to the field museum it was like 3 miles&amp;hellip; i haven&amp;rsquo;t walked that far in like 4 years&amp;hellip; hehe.. it was fun though.. i stoped in the SONY store looking for an AIBO, but it was no where to be found. I found out that the aquarium is open for free on monday, the museum of contemporary art is open for free on tuesday and the field museum is open for free on wednesday&amp;hellip; lucky days&amp;hellip; i hope to go see my friends play at northwestern&amp;hellip; and maybe i will be able to go back home to see my other friends play&amp;hellip; hmm&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>