<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rock on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/rock/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rock on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2004 07:16:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/rock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>photolog 4 life</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/05/11/photolog-4-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2004 07:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/05/11/photolog-4-life/</guid>
      <description>i can&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to get prepaid gprs. so no photolog. :( sad day. oh and before I forget. they played classic rock elevator muzak in the domestic flight here. like joe walsh and such. it ruled. I was like: &amp;ldquo;i suddenly recognize these songs.. weird.&amp;rdquo; it ruled. the same muzak is apparently everywhere. like in the bathroom and the kfc. haha. why was I in a kfc? I don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late in the evening</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/11/03/late-in-the-evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2003 10:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/11/03/late-in-the-evening/</guid>
      <description>So this weekend was great. I will expound on that later. right now I want to talk about how I am at work. it is 4:08 am. I am listening to rock on my speakers.. hanging out waiting for my work to start.. but I can&amp;rsquo;t find the ligth switch. this ALWAYS happens. I need a soda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Enemy</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/10/01/public-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2002 15:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/10/01/public-enemy/</guid>
      <description>So last night I went to go and see public enemy. It was fun however flava flav was not present. Apparently he is in jail. wtf. hehe. but the show was great anyway. kinda weird.. but chuck D rocked it hard.. then I went to a bar and my friend kept getting me drinks. I hate that. heh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rocker</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/04/10/rocker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2002 03:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/04/10/rocker/</guid>
      <description>so true. I am a rocker..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volcano 2</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2000/11/21/volcano-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2000 08:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2000/11/21/volcano-2/</guid>
      <description>Today was exciting. I did my presentation&amp;hellip; like agood boy.. after sleeping in all day.. maybe i shuldn&amp;rsquo;t have stayed up til 5 working on it&amp;hellip; well whatever.. i went to charlie&amp;rsquo;s angels and thought it ruled.. funny shit.. chicks, techno, and matrix graphics.. what more.. well i guess blow could be more.. blow seems to be a new movie that has jonny depp(sp?) and the chick from run lola run.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>