<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>http://harper.blog/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2004 09:36:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://harper.blog/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>today of all days</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-08-27-today_of_all_days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2004 09:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-08-27-today_of_all_days/</guid>
      <description>today was pretty fun. I worked. wore a tie. etc etc. it was nifty. and now I am really pretty tired. I need to get off of this crazy crazy schedule. I really dispise and hate it. i picked up an airport express. it is relly pretty cool. I like what I am abl eto do with it. especially the streaming of music. that is really really cool. I can&amp;rsquo;t really think of anything cooler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>king diamond rules.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-08-19-king_diamond_rules_/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2003 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-08-19-king_diamond_rules_/</guid>
      <description>seriously.. awesome.. you should check it out. herei am currently listening to kind diamond and lali puna on shuffle.balthus spooks me out.i need to get SOOOO much work done. it sucks. but I am trucking. weird how things go well.. then go bad&amp;hellip; then go well.. etc etc rinse repeat. whatever</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>music</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-06-03-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2003 21:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-06-03-music/</guid>
      <description>Check out this site and then buy a bunch of music there. It rules. Today was out of control. I worked a lot.. but I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I got much done. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why. it is so weird. I am all hopped up. tomorrow my mother, aunt and cousin come to visit. it will be fun. I am a bit worried about entertaining a younger person. I only know bars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>