<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 15:46:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>blue blue blue</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/09/10/blue-blue-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 15:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/09/10/blue-blue-blue/</guid>
      <description>today is pretty good. I may have gone out tooo much last night. not really late mind you. maybe too many libations. or maybe too little foods. anyway.. I feel kinda weird today. and it is a weird day. yesterday had soon many super high priority things going on it made me crazy. I want to relax today. I think I will just chill out tonight. on yea. I will. done and done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i am going to stop</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/08/12/i-am-going-to-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2004 16:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/08/12/i-am-going-to-stop/</guid>
      <description>more later - with pictures. I am tired. I finally fixed my photolog. I will start uploading pictures again. I need food so damned bad it hurts me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nobody must know my secret...</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/03/11/nobody-must-know-my-secret.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2004 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/03/11/nobody-must-know-my-secret.../</guid>
      <description>so today I got home from work and took a nap UNTIL 9:50pm. wtf. from 5:20 to 9:50. that is a long nap. that is a nights sleep for some people. those peole being me. seriously. I have to control this. heh. morgan called at like 7:30 and was like.. &amp;ldquo;hey why don&amp;rsquo;t you meet me at my work at 9:30.&amp;rdquo; I was late. haha. I slept through a 9:30pm appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dang ..</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/08/25/dang-../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2003 22:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/08/25/dang-../</guid>
      <description>work got hard. just deadlines.. hehe. stupid deadlines. I like it when work is really easy. not hard and tiring. I ended up working through lunch.. which totally sucked.. cuz I was zapped for energy as it is.. and now. broken. broken. broken. broken. I need to go and get some food. or some sleep on. I really want to get my sleep on. that would rule. tonight is live band karaoke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>time to sleep i suppose</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/08/25/time-to-sleep-i-suppose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2003 01:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/08/25/time-to-sleep-i-suppose/</guid>
      <description>i am not tired. but I am sleepy. if that makes any sense.today I went to the grocery for the first time sense april. w00t. it is exciting. I got food. and pop and beer and mor food. I like food. I shoul dgo more often. I guess I could say that I was able to go the whole summer wiht out going to the grocery. I rule. or I spend a lot of money on going out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleepy</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/05/23/sleepy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2003 19:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/05/23/sleepy/</guid>
      <description>I am tired. I need food again. In about 4 hours I am driving to the indy 500. I am excited - but tired as well. well have a good weekend yall..</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>