<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>War on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>https://harper.blog/tags/war/</link>
    <description>Recent content in War on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 11:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harper.blog/tags/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>i enjoy the strange and bizarre</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/11/15/i-enjoy-the-strange-and-bizarre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2004 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/11/15/i-enjoy-the-strange-and-bizarre/</guid>
      <description>seriously I do. my new goal (well it is the same as my old goal - but with a bit more randomness) is awkwardness, juxtoposition and hyperbole. so basiclaly my life. hah. but I am excited. for the next couple days. work is becoming ultra cool. I think their will be some nice changes soon. it just seems like their will be. like the wind is blowing change my way. I do think it is funny - I could be the veritable harbinger of death and sorrow for developers - for I have never worked anywhere where as soon as I get hired the lead developer doesn&amp;rsquo;t quit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yep.</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/05/03/yep./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2004 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/05/03/yep./</guid>
      <description>i am late for a meeting. heh. but I found this link: Rumsfeld: post-war problems of &amp;lsquo;occupation&amp;rsquo; underestimated. heh. weird eh. yea the best part is when rumsy says: &amp;ldquo;You ought to get a life&amp;rdquo; to the reporter. heh. I love our government. so conducive to not having war. hah. i feel pretty good today. i saw some friends on the train. it was pretty funny. I laughed. two mountain dews down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>night and fog</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2004/02/19/night-and-fog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2004 16:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2004/02/19/night-and-fog/</guid>
      <description>last night morgan and I watched night and fog - a really good documentary on the horrors of the german concentration camps in europe during world war II. It was the first time I had seen actual movie footage of all the bodies and such. it was quite haunting. I am not a fan of genocide. I thought that the end of the documentary was quite appropriate - with the message that the enemy is &amp;ldquo;us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so the cubs lost</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/10/16/so-the-cubs-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2003 13:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/10/16/so-the-cubs-lost/</guid>
      <description>heh. it sucks. all of my coworkers are gong to be sad. hopefully they will get over it soon. stupid sports. we should have never let them breach the level in our lives wherre they effect our emotions.. but then if they didn&amp;rsquo;t.. what good would they be. I think sports prepare us for war and conflict. whatever beowulf&amp;hellip;we have got to elect someone better for president in 2004. so I have been getting up far earlier than before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tv magic</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2003/02/20/tv-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2003 03:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2003/02/20/tv-magic/</guid>
      <description>I like watching study tv shows. like news programs or talk shows. cuz the TV magic is so artificial. It is so obviously created in a enclosed little box. For some reason it is aluring. oh.. btw the deer hunter is a crazy movie. it is on tv right now. so strange. war is a terrible thing. duh. heh. the faint is being played on MTV. rule. I wish my crib was crashed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hitler</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/09/20/hitler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2002 15:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/09/20/hitler/</guid>
      <description>This is a good cartoon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hey!</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/03/28/hey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2002 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/03/28/hey/</guid>
      <description>read this. I really don&amp;rsquo;t like war</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My birthday is today</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/03/21/my-birthday-is-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2002 21:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/03/21/my-birthday-is-today/</guid>
      <description>today is my bday. I will sing a little song: i am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24.. I am 24..  good song huh. I found a cool winamp plugin that allows me to weight songs on a playlist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams. China. and computers.. hehe</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/01/28/dreams.-china.-and-computers..-hehe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2002 15:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/01/28/dreams.-china.-and-computers..-hehe/</guid>
      <description>So I often have computer dreams. I dream of editing something in VI or Pico. I dream of installing content managment systems. I dream of mostly software. Last night I dreamt of trying to install a motherboard ethernet card into another motherboard&amp;hellip; so I had to unsolder everything out and resolder it in. heh. I don&amp;rsquo;t know hardware that well so it was hard. The other dream I had was that the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caught red handed</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/01/24/caught-red-handed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2002 13:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/01/24/caught-red-handed/</guid>
      <description>So the offending lines are: Jan 23 11:39:26 dopeman sshd: Starting sshd: Jan 23 11:39:26 dopeman sshd: /etc/ssh/sshd_config: line 56: Bad configuration option: AllowTcpForwarding Jan 23 11:39:26 dopeman sshd: /etc/ssh/sshd_config: terminating, 1 bad configuration options Jan 23 11:39:26 dopeman sshd: sshd startup failed Jan 23 11:39:27 dopeman sshd:   So I may be able to fix it without ssh. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how yet. but I imagine I will be able to hehe :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tonight..</title>
      <link>https://harper.blog/2002/01/16/tonight../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2002 02:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harper.blog/2002/01/16/tonight../</guid>
      <description>Tonight I went out with a good friend of mine. it is wierd because they are originally k*star&amp;rsquo;s friend. but somehow I grafted them over to be my friend as well. They are real nice. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how k*star doesn it. but she certainly picks god friends. all of her friends are nice. Unfortunantly I got a little ferschnickered tonight and wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to be a big help to k*star when she called me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>