<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Php on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>http://harper.blog/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Php on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2004 12:30:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://harper.blog/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>my sternum is rebeling</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-12-16-my_sternum_is_rebeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2004 12:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-12-16-my_sternum_is_rebeling/</guid>
      <description>work is fun. however for the past 12 hours - my sternum has felt like it needed to be &amp;ldquo;popped.&amp;rdquo; like a back. it sucks. it kinda hurts when I breath. I hope I am not dieing. heh. today I am not a fan of Harry Angstrom. I am annoyed at how hard he is on his son. me and my friends have been playing media mammon maniacally. it rules. basically you pick words to trade on a market - but the market value of each word is detirmined by the density of that word in the news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i don&#39;t understand why it has to be this way.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-04-12-i_dont_understand_why_it_has_to_be_this_way_/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2004 04:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2004-04-12-i_dont_understand_why_it_has_to_be_this_way_/</guid>
      <description>it seems like it could be different.  but it isn&amp;rsquo;t.  why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>photolog</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-12-11-photolog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2003 06:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-12-11-photolog/</guid>
      <description>So today I went to the dentist. it ruled. I only had one cavity. 3 years of eating candy all day long and I only get one cavity. w00t.my father is doing rather good. he is attempting to get better. slowly but surely. I imagine it is rough. for he has had open heart surgery ;)the photolog is fixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trickery</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-10-16-trickery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2003 15:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-10-16-trickery/</guid>
      <description>check out this trickery. heh. it never works. but someday.. maybe it will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>archive...</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-08-06-archive___/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2003 23:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-08-06-archive___/</guid>
      <description>so I think I redid the archive - I say maybe.. cuz it is broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meeting</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-06-25-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2003 13:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-06-25-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Next year, rather than go to the indy 500, I think I will go here.i am up, at work so early. goddamn meetings that I called. hehe. I shoudl have thought that a bit through. whatever. I am a dork.
in other news.. millions of children in the UK are goign to be really sad when they find out that the truck with all their toys.. crashed. good thing they don&amp;rsquo;t have these parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>boredom</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-05-14-boredom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2003 22:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-05-14-boredom/</guid>
      <description>Today I got bored after work and made this. It is an automagic .Klip file maker for use with the serence KlipFolio product. It allows any blog owner to make a .klip file for someone to download, so that they can syndicate their content easy and whatnot. I was tired of only having the canned content that serence provides. now I can use whatever I want.. hehe. I rule. Check out the Automagic .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>haxors</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-03-07-haxors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2003 00:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2003-03-07-haxors/</guid>
      <description>so I mad two quick html graphics hacks&amp;hellip; they are cool.  here is the first one and here is the secondOh yea&amp;hellip; I am bored. maybe I should go home. stupid after work curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love mary</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-10-30-i_love_mary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2002 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-10-30-i_love_mary/</guid>
      <description>This is so true. check out my new page. I am really interested in atom and his package - I used to love hearing about people named adam that referred to themselves as atom. I always wanted my name to be atom smasher or atom bomb.. or whatever. 
this is really interesting if you are a PHP user. Last night annie lennox one. For good reason. she looked just like annie lennox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This dude totally flips out</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-08-12-this_dude_totally_flips_out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2002 14:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-08-12-this_dude_totally_flips_out/</guid>
      <description>whooo. And the reason he lost it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes master..</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-03-29-yes_master__/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2002 17:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/oldposts/2002-03-29-yes_master__/</guid>
      <description>Yes Master&amp;hellip; yes master.. uhh.. here. here and go here.i am a sponsor here.I am supposed to get a hair cut today. I am excited and happy about that. I want to have a pretty hair cut so I can look pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>