<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>http://harper.blog/tags/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 10:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://harper.blog/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>No. 10: Medical Pot and the Iraq Veteran</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/09/26/no.-10-medical-pot-and-the-iraq-veteran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/09/26/no.-10-medical-pot-and-the-iraq-veteran/</guid>
      <description>I just read this article. It is about an Iraq Veteran and his battle with post-traumatic stress. Pretty intense - but worth reading. You can check out the article here - even better, read the full version here. Its very well written and a solid read. I guess its pretty somber, but it seems to be truth. Man. The US is in&amp;nbsp;a weird weird place right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome weekend. Pownce invites</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/07/09/awesome-weekend.-pownce-invites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2007 06:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/07/09/awesome-weekend.-pownce-invites/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was really fun. We went and saw the Police at Wrigley. Had some good foods. Hung out with friends from New York and Tokyo. And generally drank more than we should have. Totally entertaining. I also hung out with my friend Atkins - who just moved to Chicago. exciting. Hope all your weekends were just as awesome. I have a couple more Pownce invites. I am not sure that i buy it as a great service, but if you want to check it out&amp;nbsp;- tell me a joke in the comments and I will send you an invite if its a good joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing my internet.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/06/10/fixing-my-internet./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 19:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/06/10/fixing-my-internet./</guid>
      <description>Comcast is a bad person. I really hate them. On Wednesday, my internet died. So I call up and they tell me that they need to send a tech. So Friday I take off from work. The tech doesn&#39;t show. They claim he did show. long story short - I have no internet still. I am so mad. So anyway, hiromi and I have been stealing internet from neighbors and random cafes and what not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meraki: mesh wifi for the rest of us</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/06/10/meraki-mesh-wifi-for-the-rest-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 15:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/06/10/meraki-mesh-wifi-for-the-rest-of-us/</guid>
      <description>At skinnyCorp I have been trying to find a really solid wifi access point provider for awhile. Our needs are not that complicated - however we needed something that works. Originally we were using wifi to augment our wired network - before our cable pulling was completed. We used multiple Linksys WRT54G access points running DDWRT firmware using WDS. They allowed our network to spread&amp;nbsp;out to the warehouse and more importantly acted as a wireless bridge in the meantime of our network build out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goddamn. I hate Iowa Student loan people.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/03/06/goddamn.-i-hate-iowa-student-loan-people./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/03/06/goddamn.-i-hate-iowa-student-loan-people./</guid>
      <description>For the past couple weeks I have been slowly and surely reigning in all my finances and changing them to work with Hiromi and my new fancy joint account. Its pretty exciting and a big step for me in regards to finances. I usually manage my finances like I would a motorcycle - recklessly and without a helmet; but I have been trying to do everything the &amp;ldquo;correct&amp;rdquo; and have actually been reading blogs and what not to find out how to budget things efficiently and without losing money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work gocarts. yea know. the usual.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/03/02/work-gocarts.-yea-know.-the-usual./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2007 17:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/03/02/work-gocarts.-yea-know.-the-usual./</guid>
      <description>So we got gocarts at work. It is pretty awesome. I grew up with gocarts - so driving fast around is second nature and great fun. Everyday I come in and Jake is driving around our space in the gocart - zooming around desks and generally having a great time. I am surprised someone hasn&amp;rsquo;t died. but yea.
here are some videos.
The first shows me and Jake driving the gocarts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Vegan Cake</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/01/19/chocolate-vegan-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2007 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/01/19/chocolate-vegan-cake/</guid>
      <description>So at lunch today we were talking about vegan food and I remembered this excellent vegan chocolate cake recipe that my family made for the holidays. It is so good. I remember when we had bunches of non-vegan cakes and pies - this one was always the first to get eaten (the majority of my family is not vegan). Soo good. Anyway - here is the recipe - straight from my mom: Chocolate Vegan Cake</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The longest time with no Internet in recent memory</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2007/01/04/the-longest-time-with-no-internet-in-recent-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2007 06:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2007/01/04/the-longest-time-with-no-internet-in-recent-memory/</guid>
      <description>So I just got back from visiting Hiromi&#39;s relatives in the Yamanashi prefecture. We had a big New Years celebration and had a lot of fun. As you may or may not know, in Japan, New Years is quite big. It is a lot like a combination of Thanksgiving and Christmas. So while I was away for New Years, I had no access to the Internet. For almost 4 days. It was really neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pen Island Pens!</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/12/13/pen-island-pens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2006 12:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/12/13/pen-island-pens/</guid>
      <description>So I got my pen island pens last night. I am very happy with their samples. If I were going to buy a large order of pens for passing out, I would get them from pen island. They rule. Really a solid pen. I like the grip. Just to make sure that the samples were good enough I sent them to my brother Dylan&amp;nbsp;and my Dad&amp;nbsp;to test out.&amp;nbsp;Since&amp;nbsp;I sent it to Dylan&#39;s house, his wife, Sarah&amp;nbsp;was lucky enough to actually receive the shipment and sent this email to Dylan:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last night was insane: tags car is broken, hung out with cool peeps</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/11/12/last-night-was-insane-tags-car-is-broken-hung-out-with-cool-peeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2006 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/11/12/last-night-was-insane-tags-car-is-broken-hung-out-with-cool-peeps/</guid>
      <description>So yesterday was pretty fun. I got up early, played computer all afternoon. I am attempting to learn symfony - the PHP mvc framework. It looks really cool. I quite enjoy it. So I played symfony and read blogs and watched screencasts. I think I need a mac to use textmate. it looks so cool. someday.. when I get hiromi and I both macbooks.. hah
So after I ate and did laundry I went and met Morgan, Scott, Stowers, Kristin, Tag, James and James&#39; brother Juan Paulo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shutting out the Sun: an interesting book about Japan</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/10/16/shutting-out-the-sun-an-interesting-book-about-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2006 12:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/10/16/shutting-out-the-sun-an-interesting-book-about-japan/</guid>
      <description>I have been reading this awesome book called Shutting out the Sun. It is by a Knight Ridder reporter who spent a lot of time in Japan and the surrounding area. I had originally heard about the book when I caught him speaking on NPR about the topic of the book - hikikomori. It struck me as a quite interesting phenomena and with the time recently that I have spent in japan - a rather topical book to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relaxing weekend</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/10/15/relaxing-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2006 17:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/10/15/relaxing-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This weekend was great. I basically did nothing. I barely went out, saw some great performances and hung out with Matiss and Mark. It ruled.&amp;nbsp; I didn&#39;t have work on Friday. The Jakes gave us all the choice of taking off Friday or Monday - because we all worked for such a long run while moving. I decided to take Friday off to prepare for our &#34;juggling show&#34; at the Lumpen space on the southside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the most insane thing happened today on the train</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/09/18/the-most-insane-thing-happened-today-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 20:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/09/18/the-most-insane-thing-happened-today-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>It was like a dream. an annoying dream.
I got on the train at jefferson park and noticed some dumbass meatheads sitting with their suburban looking girlfriends in the middle of the train. They were being loud and obnoxious and pretty annoying. Their were multiple angry looks by the other passengers as their rockus behavior became more and more rude. So anyway - I was sitting their and reading foundation by isaac asimov - minding my own business when one of the dudes starts yelling about how some dude just flipped him off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DUNE. american heritage. 2 many djs. accidently</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/09/18/dune.-american-heritage.-2-many-djs.-accidently/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 01:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/09/18/dune.-american-heritage.-2-many-djs.-accidently/</guid>
      <description>I am watching the bbs documentary. Its amazing. I started watching clive barker&amp;rsquo;s Lord of Illusions - but it sucked. It always sucked. It sucked when i saw it in the theatre and it sucks now. So as soon as i remembered that it blew - i also remembered how awesome the BBS Doc was. So i put it in and now it is awesome. AWESOME i say.
I kinda want to run a bbs on one of my boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLEEEEEEEEP</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/09/07/sleeeeeeeep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 09:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/09/07/sleeeeeeeep/</guid>
      <description>Last night i went to bed at 6:30. I got up this morning at 7:30. I slept a lot of hours. hah. Now i am through sleeping. for at least a day. Stupid sleep.
But i am now feeling better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Simple Things You Can Do to Help Save the World</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/07/16/five-simple-things-you-can-do-to-help-save-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/07/16/five-simple-things-you-can-do-to-help-save-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Mark wrote this nice blog post called &amp;ldquo;A list of five simple things anyone can do to help the environment.&amp;rdquo; Its pretty good. Simple things that really anyone can do(i am looking at you dylan).
read more | digg story</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel/Palestine/Lebanon wtf. We are not in a good place or time.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/07/14/israel/palestine/lebanon-wtf.-we-are-not-in-a-good-place-or-time./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 11:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/07/14/israel/palestine/lebanon-wtf.-we-are-not-in-a-good-place-or-time./</guid>
      <description>This is not good. I don&amp;rsquo;t think that our world and more specifically the United States president/foriegn policy can handle an actual War in the middle east. We will act stupid and say that lebanon is a terror state.. then syria.. then iran.. and all the while israel will be &amp;ldquo;preemptively&amp;rdquo; bombing every arab/moslem state they can find. This is bad. I, of course, am not jewish/arab/moslem/israeli/palestian/labanese/nebraskan but it seems that israel attacking so many soverign countries while the world(except for the US) is shouting for them to stop is only going to lead us into a rather dark period of war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy.. and i redesigned my blog. </title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/06/20/busy..-and-i-redesigned-my-blog./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2006 04:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/06/20/busy..-and-i-redesigned-my-blog./</guid>
      <description>i am really busy right now. and have about ten posts in the draft queue. sadly i am kinda tired - so i will have to wait.
however - i have been slowly thinking about redesigning nata2. so now you get to see my first draft. kind of a rough veiw. i like the idea. but i need to fix it. hah. right now nothing works but the home page. accidently some other stuff may work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRONE! Flickr, holiday weekends, birthdays and fun. stupid stupid fun. </title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/05/30/drone-flickr-holiday-weekends-birthdays-and-fun.-stupid-stupid-fun./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2006 19:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/05/30/drone-flickr-holiday-weekends-birthdays-and-fun.-stupid-stupid-fun./</guid>
      <description>So this weekend was pretty fun. It was god damned hot and full of events. On friday i went out to dinner with matiss (since he was moving out on saturday) and chris. we went to bouna terra. It was good and we had a ncie dinner. After dinner i ran into bunches of friends and eventually made it to the SUNN 0))) show at the logan. Pretty awesome. I took a bunch of pictures and some video(1,2,3,4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a google calendar shared calendar of juggling festivals</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/05/04/i-made-a-google-calendar-shared-calendar-of-juggling-festivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2006 02:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/05/04/i-made-a-google-calendar-shared-calendar-of-juggling-festivals/</guid>
      <description>I searched and couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a really solid convention calendar so I made one. Here is the shared feed
 
Check it out. Let me know if there are additions or changes. Honestly i just wanted to get it out there. If someone wants admin access - let me know.
Also. I will be at The Stevenson Fest if anyone wants to meet up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 13:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/mobile/</guid>
      <description>Mobile phones and mobile technology has been a passion of mine since my father got a radio phone back in the day. I always find a way to scheme a new mobile phone and I am always impressed with good mobile technology.
here are some resources i have put together:  Nokia Tips and Tricks Nokia # Codes S60 Released Software List  I am sure there will be more later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff I do</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/stuff-i-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 13:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/stuff-i-do/</guid>
      <description>Hacking Stuff 
I quite enjoy manipulating and hacking stuff. It could a web application, learning AJAX or XSLT or taking apart the latest awesome consumer appliance. Ever since before college I have been interested in writing software, taking stuff apart and making new things.  Here is a short history since 2001 of stuff that I have been concertrating on hacking or manipulating.  2006 ~ We shall see&amp;hellip; 2005 ~ Play Station Portable - Having seen the jakes PSPs while working on squidoo, i was impressed with what they were able to do with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S60 3rd edition app list</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/s60-3rd-edition-app-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 13:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/s60-3rd-edition-app-list/</guid>
      <description>My friend jacob got a Nokia 3250 on my recommendation and was disappointed that it didn&amp;rsquo;t have as many apps as my N70 did. So while scouring the internet and looking for applications for him i decided that i would create an application list for the Symbian 3rd edition phones.  Here it goes:  Handy Weather - Putty -  If you have found software that is hopefully missing from this list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia # Codes</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/nokia-#-codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 13:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/nokia-#-codes/</guid>
      <description>Here are a bundle of # codes for nokia phones. Quite a few of them work for my N70 and my 7610 so i imagine they work on a lot of phones - but use at your own risk.  *#0000# Check firmware version*3370# This Nokia code activates Enhanced Full Rate Codec (EFR) - Your Nokia cell phone uses the best sound quality but talk time is reduced my approx. 5%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>38 S60 tips and tricks </title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/38-s60-tips-and-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 13:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/11/38-s60-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
      <description>So now that everyone is finally interested in getting a symbian phone - i decided to unearth some tricks and what not for symbian phones.
I have tried most of these. I am not quite sure where i got this list - probably from some yahoo group or some site years ago when i got my 7610. Most of it works on my N70 so it should all be still current.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About done. sick. maxbar. barbelith.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/04/05/about-done.-sick.-maxbar.-barbelith./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2006 00:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/04/05/about-done.-sick.-maxbar.-barbelith./</guid>
      <description>Today was a long day. I have been going to bed so early and then getting up early. It has been nice. But I need to figure out the point of sleep moderation - or i need to get well. It seems that every day around 11 o clock i get kinda sick. Like my throat gets irratated and i cough a bit more. Probably just weak still from my fight with the cold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i am sleepy</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/01/29/i-am-sleepy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2006 06:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/01/29/i-am-sleepy/</guid>
      <description>yes. i am. i have a blog entry brewing in me. i will post it tomorrow. while i work on yellowikis.us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i am a polyphasic sleeper. woot.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/07/21/i-am-a-polyphasic-sleeper.-woot./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2005 19:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/07/21/i-am-a-polyphasic-sleeper.-woot./</guid>
      <description>After some discussion with my new friend heath he pointed me to this and then i found this link that had seen before.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think that the uberman schedule is for me. but i do think that polyphasic sleep is good.
hehe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iBook picture frame</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/07/20/ibook-picture-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/07/20/ibook-picture-frame/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ahhhhhh</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/07/19/ahhhhhh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 13:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/07/19/ahhhhhh/</guid>
      <description>i just woke up and my eyes don&amp;rsquo;t work yet!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nyc</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/06/19/nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2005 03:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/06/19/nyc/</guid>
      <description>i will sort of be in nyc for the next week. contact me if you are around. i may be able to play.
play play play.
i just saw batman begins. quite nice. really great action sequences, and my brother is quite right. VERy DARK. matiss would love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3gcoding part 2</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/05/19/3gcoding-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 01:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/05/19/3gcoding-part-2/</guid>
      <description>i guess i should start blogging on here again. it has been a couple months and i have kinda fallen out of the mobile game. My new interest in regards to mobile is data and how it can spawn the mobile market. For instance i want to see where text messaging will go. i have some ideas. stay tuned. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3gcoding part 2</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/05/19/3gcoding-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2005 01:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/05/19/3gcoding-part-2/</guid>
      <description>i guess i should start blogging on here again. it has been a couple months and i have kinda fallen out of the mobile game. My new interest in regards to mobile is data and how it can spawn the mobile market. For instance i want to see where text messaging will go. i have some ideas. stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>driveby</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/05/11/driveby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 01:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/05/11/driveby/</guid>
      <description>there were gunshots today at 2:20 or so. like semi auto or something. nuts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/05/10/sleep./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2005 23:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/05/10/sleep./</guid>
      <description>i am tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sleepy. my birthday was good</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/03/21/sleepy.-my-birthday-was-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 23:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/03/21/sleepy.-my-birthday-was-good/</guid>
      <description>this years birthday ruled. it was nice to celebrate it with everyone. happy happy.
tonight we went and got Ethiopian food. it was nice.
now to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today was hell.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/03/14/today-was-hell./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2005 20:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/03/14/today-was-hell./</guid>
      <description>a mess was caused. I fixed it - but it still was a mess. stupid messes.
now it is time TO ROCK. R O C K.
I screwed up my work computer. I have a dialog pasted on the screen and it isn&#39;t leaving. dumb dumb. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>long ago</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/03/12/long-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2005 15:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/03/12/long-ago/</guid>
      <description>i had these pictures forever - but I was unable to put them up. first I thought I lost my camera battery. then I found it. then I was dumb. then dumber. then I figured it all out. for the record. iphoto is not better than picasa. picasa is real real nice. the absolute integration of iphoto is dope. but picasa is better. a lot better. heh.
 so here are some pictures from awhile ago:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ipod Mini, Mac Mini and padded rooms.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/02/01/ipod-mini-mac-mini-and-padded-rooms./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2005 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/02/01/ipod-mini-mac-mini-and-padded-rooms./</guid>
      <description>So i got one of those free ipod minis. It was stupid, those are such scams. it took a long time - cuz i didn&amp;#8217;t really care. but seriously. it isn&amp;#8217;t worth doing. you might as well just save your money and buy one. odn&amp;#8217;t get me wrong - it is free. but you are inadvertently selling out your fiends in the process. ;) I also picked up a mac mini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ipod Mini, Mac Mini and padded rooms.</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2005/02/01/ipod-mini-mac-mini-and-padded-rooms./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2005 10:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2005/02/01/ipod-mini-mac-mini-and-padded-rooms./</guid>
      <description>So i got one of those free ipod minis. It was stupid, those are such scams. it took a long time - cuz i didn&amp;rsquo;t really care. but seriously. it isn&amp;rsquo;t worth doing. you might as well just save your money and buy one. odn&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong - it is free. but you are inadvertently selling out your fiends in the process. ;)
I also picked up a mac mini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2004/06/29/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2004 02:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2004/06/29/updates/</guid>
      <description>So i have been really busy with a bunch of random and unrelated things. Basically i haven&amp;#8217;t engaged in anything mobile technology at all - which is annoying. i need to play more. matiss just got a phone with a camera. so i imagine i will be creating a simple way to do a photoblog for him. i hope anyway it will go well. i really need to acquire or figure out how to quickly get a sms gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2004/06/29/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2004 02:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2004/06/29/updates/</guid>
      <description>So i have been really busy with a bunch of random and unrelated things. Basically i haven&amp;rsquo;t engaged in anything mobile technology at all - which is annoying. i need to play more. matiss just got a phone with a camera. so i imagine i will be creating a simple way to do a photoblog for him. i hope anyway it will go well. i really need to acquire or figure out how to quickly get a sms gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jabra bluetooth headset</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2004/01/07/jabra-bluetooth-headset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 11:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2004/01/07/jabra-bluetooth-headset/</guid>
      <description>so the other day I decided to pick up a Jabra Freespeak bluetooth headset for my t610. When wearing it I feel as though I am in the future. I thought about getting the digital bluespoon but i felt bad paying more for the headset than i did for the phone. so i guess that will have to wait for when i get my 6600.
here is an awesome review of the bluespoon here is a poor review of the jabra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mms 2 blog</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2003/12/10/mms-2-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2003 12:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2003/12/10/mms-2-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I really like the idea of mobile blogging and haven&amp;rsquo;t been too keen on using my keypad to do an entry on my blog. A friend showed me his &lt;a href=&#34;http://bryan.textamerica.com/&#34;&gt;moblog&lt;/a&gt; that he made using his &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nokia.com/nokia/0,,2273,00.html&#34;&gt;3650&lt;/a&gt; and i thought that it couldn&amp;rsquo;t possibly be that hard to create a similar thing using the mms message sent from the phone. As far as i can tell - the mms message is composed of fancy headers and then the payload as an attachment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porting from sprint to t-mobile</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2003/12/05/porting-from-sprint-to-t-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2003 01:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2003/12/05/porting-from-sprint-to-t-mobile/</guid>
      <description>On the LNP day last month i immediately ported from sprint to t-mobile. I had been with sprint for 4 years and was appreciative of their &amp;ldquo;3g&amp;rdquo; technology. but after gettgin completely screwed one too many times i decided to switch. I had a tough time figuring out which provider to go with, although i had narrowed the phone down to the t610.
I really liked the look and shape of the t610.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>