<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General Technology Hacking Diy Make Ambient Embedded Nabaztag Takeapart Wifi Led on Writing by Harper Reed</title>
    <link>http://harper.blog/tags/general-technology-hacking-diy-make-ambient-embedded-nabaztag-takeapart-wifi-led/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General Technology Hacking Diy Make Ambient Embedded Nabaztag Takeapart Wifi Led on Writing by Harper Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2006 20:45:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://harper.blog/tags/general-technology-hacking-diy-make-ambient-embedded-nabaztag-takeapart-wifi-led/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the nabaztag</title>
      <link>http://harper.blog/2006/02/27/investigating-the-nabaztag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2006 20:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://harper.blog/2006/02/27/investigating-the-nabaztag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got my gumstix today and was lauding the fanciness of the smallest comptuer i have EVER seen, explaining to my coworker Dan how i was going to build an &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ambientdevices.com/&#34;&gt;ambient orb&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&#34;http://nabaztag.com/&#34;&gt;nabaztag &lt;/a&gt;like device that will integrate with my &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nokia.com/n70&#34;&gt;bluetooth phone&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href=&#34;http://asteriskathome.sourceforge.net/&#34;&gt;pbx&lt;/a&gt;. he was impressed of course ;) - and told me that our coworker jake already had a &lt;a href=&#34;http://nabaztag.com/&#34;&gt;nabaztag&lt;/a&gt;. I was like &amp;ldquo;WOAH.&amp;rdquo; Those little punks are hard to get here in the states. So i talked to jake and he brought it in for lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.flickr.com/photos/natatwo/105460276/in/photostream&#34;&gt;&lt;img align=&#34;right&#34; src=&#34;http://static.flickr.com/44/105460276_f112fd265d_m.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got it - it wasn&amp;rsquo;t booting correctly, saying there was a problem by flashing yellow. hah. It coudln&amp;rsquo;t find its home WIFI net and obviously couldn&amp;rsquo;t access &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.skinnycorp.com&#34;&gt;skinnyCorps&lt;/a&gt;. So i looked at all the documentation and found that it is REALLY easy to fix.  All you do is unplug it, hold the top button down, plug it in and then access the nabaztag wifi network. Then load up your browser and access the webpage for easy nabaztag configuration - including a nice &amp;ldquo;scan networks&amp;rdquo; feature. Personally  I feel that this is one of the coolest features of almost any wifi gadget out there. Could you imagine if the Airport express was as easy to setup, or those bastard wifi cameras? I mean really. How mcuh time could i have saved instead of unhooking the camera and plugging it into ethernet. So much time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway. So while we were trying to get it to work, jake let me know that it had been thrown and may have been broken. How sad. So i immediately offered to take it apart and fix er up.  So I did&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>